Guide to the Isidore Sydney Falk Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Professional Activities, 1919-1979; Series II; 44 linear feet (107 boxes)
  - Canal Zone Government (Panama)
    - Survey Materials
      - Health Bureau
        - Republic of Panama: correspondence and notes re: services provided, 1955-1957 (Box 102, Folder 1173)
      - Vital Statistics
        - "Census of a Population", 1950 (Box 102, Folder 1174)
        - Working papers re: mortality tables, 1950-1957 (Box 103, Folder 1175)
        - Tables re: working population, 1954-1957 (Box 103, Folder 1176)
        - General working papers, 1955-1957 (Box 103, Folder 1177)
        - Tables re: birthrates, 1956-1957 (Box 103, Folder 1178)
    - Mission reports
      - "Estimates of the Canal Zone Population and of Persons Eligible for Service in the Health Facilities of the Canal Zone Government 1954-1966" (I.S.F.), 1957 May (Box 103, Folder 1179)
      - "Study of Health Services and Requirements in the Canal Zone" (I.S.F.), 1957 September 14-16 (Box 103, Folder 1180)
      - Working papers re: Appendix A, 1957 (Box 103, Folder 1181)
      - "A Survey of Health Services and Facilities in the Canal Zone" (I.S.F.), 1958 January (Box 103, Folder 1182)
    - Reference files
      - Print material, 1948-1959 (Box 103, Folder 1183)
      - "A Bibliography Covering Medical Activity on the Canal Zone 1904-1954", Circa 1954 (Box 103, Folder 1184)
      - Newsclippings, 1955-1958 (Box 103, Folder 1185-1186)
      - Print material, undated (Box 103, Folder 1187)
  - United Steelworkers of America
    - Correspondence and Subject Files
      - A (Box 103, Folder 1188)
      - Allegheny General Hospital, 1959-1960 (Box 103, Folder 1189)
      - American Dental Association, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 1190)
      - American Hospital Association, 1960-1967 (Box 103, Folder 1191)
      - American Medical Association, 1960-1962 (Box 103, Folder 1192)
      - American Osteopathic Association, 1966-1967 (Box 103, Folder 1193)
      - Associated Hospital Service of New York, 1960, 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 1194)
      - Associated Hospital Service of Philadelphia, 1958-1961 (Box 103, Folder 1195)
      - B (Box 103, Folder 1196)
      - Birmingham (Alabama), 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 1197)
      - Blue Cross Association, 1958 October-Dec, 1959 January-Jun, 1959 October-1961, undated, 1959 (Box 104, Folder 1198-1201)
      - Blue Cross of Western Pennsylvania, 1958-1968 (Box 104, Folder 1202-1204)
      - Blue Shield Commission, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 1205)
      - Blue Shield Medical Care Plans, 1959 (Box 104, Folder 1206)
      - Brewster, Agnes W., 1959-1962, undated (Box 104, Folder 1207)
      - C (Box 104, Folder 1208)
      - Charleroi-Monessen Hospital, Centerville (Pennsylvania), 1964 (Box 104, Folder 1209)
      - City of Hope Pilot Medical Center, Philadelphia, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1210)
      - Clague, Ewan, 1959-1961 (Box 104, Folder 1211)
      - Cleveland, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 1212)
      - Columbia University, 1958-1961 (Box 104, Folder 1213)
      - Community Health Association, Detroit, 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 1214)
      - Community Health Care Center Plan, New Haven, 1972-1973 (Box 104, Folder 1215)
      - Community Health Center, Inc., Two Harbors (Minnesota), 1960 (Box 104, Folder 1216)
      - Community Health Foundation, Cleveland, 1962, 1964, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1217)
      - Duzak, Thomas F., 1980 (Box 104, Folder 1218)
      - Esselstyn, Caldwell B., 1960-1963 (Box 104, Folder 1219)
      - F (Box 104, Folder 1220)
      - Foundation for Medical Care of San Joaquin County, Circa 1961, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 1221-1222)
      - Franklin Square Hospital, Baltimore, 1959 Feb, 1959-1962 (Box 105, Folder 1223-1224)
      - G (Box 105, Folder 1225)
      - Greenberg, Bernard, 1958-1964, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 1226)
      - Group Health Association, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 105, Folder 1227)
      - Group Health Association of America, Inc., 1960 (Box 105, Folder 1228)
      - Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound, Seattle, 1959-1960, 1962, 1964 (Box 105, Folder 1229)
      - Group Health of Arizona, 1972-1973 (Box 105, Folder 1230)
      - H (Box 105, Folder 1231)
      - Health Insurance Plan of Greater New York, 1959-1961 (Box 105, Folder 1232)
      - Health maintenance organization reviews, 1977-1979 (Box 105, Folder 1233)
      - Homestead (Pennsylvania) Hospital, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 1234)
      - Hospital Association of Pennsylvania, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 1235)
      - Hospital Council of Philadelphia, 1959-1960 (Box 105, Folder 1236)
      - Hospital Council of Western Pennsylvania, 1959, 1962, undated (Box 105, Folder 1237)
      - Hospital Planning Association of Allegheny County (Pennsylvania), 1960, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 1238)
      - Inland Steel Company, 1958-1963 (Box 105, Folder 1239)
      - InterStudy, 1979 July-August (Box 105, Folder 1240)
      - Johns Hopkins Hospital, Baltimore, 1960-1962 (Box 105, Folder 1241)
      - Kaiser Foundation Health Plan, 1959-1961, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 1242)
      - Kennecott Copper Company, 1961-1962 (Box 105, Folder 1243)
      - Krantz, Goldie, 1959-1962 (Box 105, Folder 1244)
      - L (Box 105, Folder 1245)
      - Latimer, Murray W., 1958 (Box 105, Folder 1246)
      - Life Extension Institute, undated (Box 105, Folder 1247)
      - M (Box 105, Folder 1248)
      - McNerney, Walter J., 1959-1961 (Box 106, Folder 1249)
      - Major medical insurance, 1959-1961 (Box 106, Folder 1250)
      - Marshall, Matthew, 1959-1965, undated (Box 106, Folder 1251)
      - Medical Foundation of Bellaire (Ohio), 1960 (Box 106, Folder 1252)
      - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., 1958-1961 (Box 106, Folder 1253)
      - Montefiore Hospital, New York, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 1254)
      - Montefiore Hospital, Pittsburgh, Circa 1961 (Box 106, Folder 1255)
      - National Association of Blue Shield Plans, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 1256)
      - O (Box 106, Folder 1257)
      - Ohio Medical Indemnity, Inc., 1963 (Box 106, Folder 1258)
      - Ohio Senate Bill 461 (Community Health Bill), 1959 (Box 106, Folder 1259)
      - Opinion Research Corp., 1961 (Box 106, Folder 1260)
      - P (Box 106, Folder 1261)
      - Penn Group Health Plan, 1975 May-Nov, undated (Box 106, Folder 1262-1263)
      - Pennsylvania Blue Shield, 1958-1969, undated (Box 107, Folder 1264-1266)
      - Pennsylvania Blue Shield, rate hearings, 1960, 1960 June 29, 1960 circa August (Box 107, Folder 1267-1269)
      - Pennsylvania Hospital Study Commission, 1960 (Box 107, Folder 1270)
      - Pennsylvania Medical Society, 1960 (Box 107, Folder 1271)
      - Pennsylvania Senate Bill 844 (enabling legislation), 1959-1961 (Box 107, Folder 1272)
      - Pilot project areas, 1959-1960 (Box 107, Folder 1273)
      - Provident Life and Accident Co., 1960 (Box 107, Folder 1274)
      - Republic Steel Co., 1958-1959, 1962 (Box 107, Folder 1275)
      - Riverside County (California) Medical Association, 1961 (Box 107, Folder 1276)
      - Rosenfield, Isadore, 1959 (Box 107, Folder 1277)
      - Russelton Medical Group, New Kensington (Pennsylvania), 1961 (Box 107, Folder 1278)
      - S (Box 107, Folder 1279)
      - St. Louis Labor Health Institute, 1960 (Box 107, Folder 1280)
      - Sault Ste. Marie (Ontario) and District Group Health Association, 1959 (Box 107, Folder 1281)
      - Sault Ste. Marie (Ontario) and District Group Health Association, 1960 January-June (Box 108, Folder 1282-1283)
      - Sault Ste. Marie (Ontario) and District Group Health Association, 1960 July-December, 1961 January-December (Box 108, Folder 1284-1288)
      - Sault Ste. Marie (Ontario) and District Group Health Association, 1962 January-December (Box 108, Folder 1289-1291)
      - Sault Ste. Marie (Ontario) and District Group Health Association, 1963 (Box 108, Folder 1292)
      - Senturia, Joseph J., 1958-1962 (Box 108, Folder 1293)
      - Sheps, Cecil G., 1959-1961 (Box 109, Folder 1294)
      - Small Hospital Consultants, Inc., 1959, 1961, undated (Box 109, Folder 1295)
      - T (Box 109, Folder 1296)
      - Tomayko, John F., 1958-1974 (Box 109, Folder 1297)
      - United Auto Workers, 1961-1964 (Box 109, Folder 1298)
      - United Rubber Workers of America, 1959 (Box 109, Folder 1299)
      - United States National Health Survey, 1959-1960 (Box 109, Folder 1300)
      - United States Steel and Carnegie Pension Fund, 1963-1964 (Box 109, Folder 1301)
      - University of Pittsburgh, 1958-1961 (Box 109, Folder 1302)
      - W (Box 109, Folder 1303)
      - Washington (state) Physicians Service, Circa 1961 (Box 109, Folder 1304)
      - Worcester (Massachusetts), 1961 (Box 109, Folder 1305)
    - Administrative Papers
      - Constitutional conventions
        - Resolution re: health care study and proceedings, 1958 September (Box 109, Folder 1306)
        - Resolutions, releases and related material, 1960 September (Box 109, Folder 1307)
        - Proceedings and related material, 1962 September (Box 110, Folder 1308)
      - Contracts and proposals, 1958-1959 August (Box 110, Folder 1309)
      - Miscellaneous clippings re: health benefits, 1958-1960 (Box 110, Folder 1310)
      - Human Relations Committee, Joint Subcommittee on Medical Care
        - Establishing memo, 1959 October (Box 110, Folder 1311)
        - Agendas, minutes and correspondence, 1960, 1961 January-Dec, 1962 January-June (Box 110, Folder 1311-1316)
        - Report re: insurance and medical care problems, 1962 January 22 (Box 110, Folder 1317)
        - Agendas, minutes and correspondence, 1962 September-1963 (Box 110, Folder 1318)
        - Progress report, 1963 April (Box 110, Folder 1319)
        - Report re: physicians' charges and Blue Shield benefits, 1963 July (Box 110, Folder 1320)
        - Report re: steel industry health insurance, 1963 August (Box 110, Folder 1321)
        - Agendas, minutes and correspondence, 1964 January-June (Box 111, Folder 1322)
        - Report re: group practice, 1964 July (Box 111, Folder 1323)
        - Report re: group practice, background and revision material, Circa 1964 July (Box 111, Folder 1324)
        - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1964 August-December (Box 111, Folder 1325)
      - Contracts and proposals, 1959 October-1960 (Box 111, Folder 1326)
      - Correspondence re: insurance ?booklet" study, 1959 (Box 111, Folder 1327)
      - Correspondence re: medical benefits survey, 1959 (Box 111, Folder 1328)
      - International Wage Policy Committee: correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 111, Folder 1329)
      - Correspondence re: comparison of U.S.W.A. and other union benefits, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 1330)
      - Correspondence re: U.S.W.A. health study report, 1960-1961 (Box 111, Folder 1331)
      - Conference, "The Health Business: Direction, Please?": correspondence, outline and notes (I.S.F.), 1961 March (Box 111, Folder 1332)
      - Staff Development and Training Program
        - Photographs and reference material, 1962-1968, undated (Box 111, Folder 1333)
        - Correspondence and lecture outlines, 1966-1972 (Box 111, Folder 1334)
      - Contracts and proposals, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 1335)
      - Conference on Prepayment and Delivery of Health Care: correspondence and print material, 1972 April (Box 112, Folder 1336)
    - Working Papers
      - Background
        - Data re: steel company benefit programs, 1953, circa 1958-1959 (Box 112, Folder 1337)
        - Data re: steelworker population concentration, 1958-1959 (Box 112, Folder 1338)
        - Papers re: survey topics and methods, 1958-1959 (Box 112, Folder 1339)
        - Desk diary notes (I.S.F.), 1958-1961 (Box 112, Folder 1340)
      - 1958-1960
        - Blue Cross-Blue Shield
          - Associated Hospital Service of Philadelphia: general data, 1958-1959 (Box 112, Folder 1341)
          - Blue Cross Association: general data, 1959-1960, undated (Box 112, Folder 1342)
          - Blue Cross Association: experience tables, Circa 1959 (Box 112, Folder 1343)
          - Blue Cross Association: work sheets, Circa 1959 (Box 112, Folder 1344)
          - Blue Cross Commission: utilization tables, 1958-1960 (Box 112, Folder 1345)
          - Blue Cross of Western Pennsylvania: general data, 1958-1960 (Box 112, Folder 1346)
          - Blue Shield Medical Care Plans: experience tables, 1959-1960 (Box 112, Folder 1347)
          - Blue Shield Medical Care Plans: worksheets, Circa 1959 (Box 112, Folder 1348)
          - Blue Shield survey: surgical data (Allentown, Baltimore, Birmingham), 1959 (Box 112, Folder 1349)
          - Blue Shield survey: surgical data (Boston, Buffalo, Chicago), 1959 (Box 112, Folder 1350)
          - Blue Shield survey: surgical data (Indiana, Los Angeles, Michigan), 1959 (Box 112, Folder 1351)
          - Blue Shield survey: surgical data (Ohio, Pittsburgh, St. Paul), 1959 (Box 113, Folder 1352)
          - Blue Shield survey: worksheets, Circa 1959 (Box 113, Folder 1353)
          - Pennsylvania Blue Shield: general data, 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 1354)
          - United Steelworkers of America, District 33 Syndicate Blue Cross-Blue Shield Plans: experience tables, 1959 (Box 113, Folder 1355)
        - Commercial insurance
          - American Can Company: general data, Circa 1959-1960 (Box 113, Folder 1356)
          - Commercial insurance: miscellaneous notes and worksheets, 1959-1960 (Box 113, Folder 1357)
          - Commercial insurance: tabulations, Circa 1959 (Box 113, Folder 1358)
          - Continental Can Company: general data, Circa 1959-1960 (Box 113, Folder 1359)
          - Inland Steel Company: general data, 1959-1960 (Box 113, Folder 1360)
          - "Intensive Study" form, 1958 December (Box 113, Folder 1361)
          - Republic Steel Company: general data, 1959-1960 (Box 113, Folder 1362)
        - Special studies
          - Major medical insurance: general data and background material, Circa 1959-1960. (Box 113, Folder 1363)
          - Sault Ste. Marie (Ontario) and District Group Health Association: general data, 1959-1960 (Box 113, Folder 1364)
          - United Steelworkers of America, insurance "booklet" study: tables, 1959 (Box 113, Folder 1365)
          - United Steelworkers of America, study comparing U.S.W.A. and other union benefits: general data, Circa 1959 (Box 114, Folder 1366)
          - Miscellaneous notes and working papers, 1959-1960 (Box 114, Folder 1367)
      - 1961-1973
        - Bethlehem Steel Company: coverage reports, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 1368)
        - Blue Cross Association: experience and utilization tables, 1961 (Box 114, Folder 1369)
        - Blue Cross of Western Pennsylvania: general data, 1961-1968, undated (Box 114, Folder 1370-1371)
        - Cleveland-Baltimore study: general data, Circa 1961 (Box 114, Folder 1372)
        - Community Health Care Center Plan, New Haven: general data, Circa 1971-1972 (Box 114, Folder 1373)
        - Gary (Indiana)-Chicago study: general data, 1962-1963, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 1374)
        - Gary (Indiana)-Chicago study: tables, Circa 1962 November (Box 114, Folder 1375)
        - Inland Steel Company: coverage and experience tables, 1962, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 1376)
        - Kaiser Foundation Health Plan: general data, Circa 1961, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 1377)
        - Pennsylvania Blue Shield: general data, 1961-1964 September (Box 114, Folder 1378)
        - Pennsylvania Blue Shield: general data, 1964 November-Dec, 1965-1967, undated (Box 114, Folder 1379-1380)
        - Pennsylvania Blue Shield, claim form study: notes and exhibits, 1961 (Box 114, Folder 1381)
        - Republic Steel Company: coverage tables, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 1382)
        - Sault Ste. Marie (Ontario) and District Group Health Association: general data, 1961-1962, undated (Box 115, Folder 1383)
        - United States Steel and Carnegie Pension Fund: general data, 1961-1963, 1964, 1972-1973 (Box 115, Folder 1384-1386)
        - Miscellaneous papers and reference material re: independent health plans, Circa 1961, 1965 (Box 115, Folder 1387)
    - Reports and Publications
      - Preliminary report: typescript, 1959 April (Box 115, Folder 1388)
      - Preliminary report: draft and revision material, 1959 (Box 115, Folder 1389)
      - "The Steelworkers Survey Their Health Services": speech text and reprint, 1959 Oct, 1961 January (Box 115, Folder 1390)
      - "A Formulation of Labor's Views": reprint, 1959 December (Box 115, Folder 1391)
      - "Special Study on the Medical Care Program for Steelworkers and Their Families": published convention report, 1960 September (Box 115, Folder 1392)
      - "Special Study on the Medical Care Program for Steelworkers and Their Families": draft charts and tables, 1960 May-August (Box 115, Folder 1393)
      - "Special Study on the Medical Care Program for Steelworkers and Their Families": draft text (conclusions, summary and chap. I-II), 1960 May-August (Box 115, Folder 1394)
      - "Special Study on the Medical Care Program for Steelworkers and Their Families": draft text (chap. III VIII), 1960 May-August (Box 115, Folder 1395)
      - "A Survey of the Medical Care Insurance Program for Steelworkers and Their Dependents": typescript (chap I-IV), 1960-1961 (Box 116, Folder 1396)
      - "A Survey of the Medical Care Insurance Program for Steelworkers and Their Dependents": typescript (chap. V), 1960-1961 (Box 116, Folder 1397)
      - "A Survey of the Medical Care Insurance Program for Steelworkers and Their Dependents": typescript (chap. VI), 1960-1961 (Box 116, Folder 1398)
      - "A Survey of the Medical Care Insurance Program for Steelworkers and Their Dependents": draft text material, 1959-1960 (Box 116, Folder 1399)
      - "A Survey of the Medical Care Insurance Program for Steelworkers and Their Dependents": draft appendix tables, Circa 1961 (Box 116, Folder 1400)
      - "A Survey of the Medical Care Insurance Program for Steelworkers and Their Dependents": revision material, undated (Box 116, Folder 1401)
      - "Medical Care Committee of the Basic Steel Industry Meets With Hospital and Medical Associations": typescript, tear sheet, 1961 Jan, March (Box 116, Folder 1402)
      - "Survey of the Staff Health Plan, United Steelworkers of America-Life Extension Examiners": draft, 1961 March (Box 116, Folder 1403)
      - "Steelworkers Study West Coast Health Plans": typescript, 1961 September (Box 116, Folder 1404)
      - "Special Report on Medical Care for Steelworkers and Their Families Through Group Practice Prepayment Plans": draft, 1964 August (Box 116, Folder 1405)
      - "Health Insurance in Steel Industry Employments" (I.S.F. and R.H. Falk): preliminary draft, Circa 1966 August (Box 117, Folder 1406)
      - Miscellaneous fragmentary and unidentified drafts, 1958, 1964, undated (Box 117, Folder 1407)
      - Miscellaneous notes and references, undated (Box 117, Folder 1408)
      - Miscellaneous unidentified tables, undated (Box 117, Folder 1409)
  - Yale University, Department of Epidemiology and Public Health
    - Correspondence with Edward M. Cohart, Anthony M.-M. Payne and others re: appointment, 1960-1961 (Box 117, Folder 1410)
    - Correspondence re: Anna M.R. Lauder Professorship, 1962-1963 (Box 117, Folder 1411)
    - Correspondence re: appointment, 1965-1980 (Box 117, Folder 1412)
    - Correspondence re: annual reports, 1966-1968 (Box 117, Folder 1413)
    - Course Materials
      - Principles and Practice of Public Health 140: schedule, topic outline and related course material, 1961 September 20-1962 January 24 (Box 117, Folder 1414)
      - Program in Hospital Administration 172: schedules, 1961 September 20-1962 January 25 (Box 117, Folder 1415)
      - Medical Care 170
        - Course outline and schedules, 1961 September 22-1962 January 26 (Box 117, Folder 1416)
        - Lecture 1: outline, text and background material, 1961 September 22 (Box 117, Folder 1417)
        - Lectures 2-4: outline and texts, 1961 September 29, October 6 13 (Box 117, Folder 1418)
        - Lectures 5-6: outline, notes and background material, 1961 October 27, November 3 (Box 117, Folder 1419)
        - Lecture 9: outline and background material, 1961 November 17 (Box 117, Folder 1420)
        - Lectures 10-11: outline and background material, 1961 November 24, December 1 (Box 117, Folder 1421)
        - Lectures 12-13: notes and background material, 1961 December 8, 15 (Box 117, Folder 1422)
        - Lectures 14-16: outline, notes and background material, 1962 January 5, 12 (Box 117, Folder 1423)
        - Lecture 17: outline, notes and background material, 1962 January 26 (Box 117, Folder 1424)
      - Program in Hospital Administration 172: schedule and background material, 1962 January 29-May 17 (Box 117, Folder 1425)
      - Medical Care in the United States 171
        - Schedules, course outline and list of students, 1962 January 30-May 29 (Box 117, Folder 1426)
        - Lecture 1: outline and notes, 1962 January 30 (Box 117, Folder 1427)
        - Lecture 2: outline, notes and correspondence, 1962 February 6 (Box 117, Folder 1428)
        - Lecture 3: outline, notes and correspondence, 1962 February 13 (Box 117, Folder 1429)
        - Lecture 4: outline, notes and correspondence, 1962 February 20 (Box 117, Folder 1430)
        - Lecture 5: notes 1962, February 27 (Box 117, Folder 1431)
        - Lecture 6: outline and background material, 1962 March 6 (Box 117, Folder 1432)
        - Lecture 7: notes and correspondence, 1962 March 13 (Box 117, Folder 1433)
        - Lecture 8: notes, 1962 April 3 (Box 117, Folder 1434)
        - Lecture 9: outline, 1962 April 10 (Box 117, Folder 1435)
        - Lecture 10: notes, outline and text, 1962 April 17 (Box 117, Folder 1436)
        - Lectures 11-12: notes and texts, 1962 April 24, May 1 (Box 117, Folder 1437)
        - Lecture 13: outline and text, 1962 May 8, 15, 22 (Box 117, Folder 1438)
        - Lecture 14: outline and background material, 1962 May 29 (Box 118, Folder 1439)
      - Medical Care and Hospital Administration 172: schedules and background material, 1962 September 17-1963 January 24 (Box 118, Folder 1440)
      - Medical Care 170
        - Schedules and course outline, 1962 September 25-1963 January 22 (Box 118, Folder 1441)
        - Background material, 1962 September 25-1963 January 22 (Box 118, Folder 1442)
        - Correspondence and reading lists, 1962 September 22-1963 January 22 (Box 118, Folder 1443)
        - Lectures 1-2: texts, 1962 September 25, October 2 (Box 118, Folder 1444)
        - Lecture 3: outline, text and background material, 1962 October 9 (Box 118, Folder 1445)
        - Lecture 4: outline and notes, 1962 October 23 (Box 118, Folder 1446)
        - Lecture 5: outline, text (I.S.F., E.R. Weinerman), 1962 October 30 (Box 118, Folder 1447)
        - Lecture 6: outline, notes and text, 1962 November 6 (Box 118, Folder 1448)
        - Lecture 7: text (E.R. Weinerman), 1962 November 13 (Box 118, Folder 1449)
        - Lecture 8: text, notes and background material, 1962 November 20 (Box 118, Folder 1450)
        - Lecture 9: outline, notes and text, 1962 November 26 (Box 118, Folder 1451)
        - Lectures 1O-12: outlines, notes and background material (I.S.F., E.R. Weinerman), 1962 December 4, 11, 18 (Box 118, Folder 1452)
        - Lecture 13: outline and notes, 1963 January 8 (Box 118, Folder 1453)
        - Lectures 14-15: outline, notes and background material, 1963 January 15, 22 (Box 118, Folder 1454)
      - "Developing a Program of Research in Medical Care," lecture: outline, notes and background material, 1962 December 18 (Box 118, Folder 1455)
      - Medical Care and Hospital Administration 172: schedules, 1963 January 28-March 15 (Box 118, Folder 1456)
      - Medical Care in the United States 171
        - Schedules, topic outline and student list, 1963 January 29-May 28 (Box 118, Folder 1457)